{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "明天" ,
      "answer": "Míngtiān | tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "有",
      "answer": "Yǒu | to have"
    },
    {
      "question": "时间" ,
      "answer": "Shíjiān | time"
    },
    {
      "question": "说",
      "answer": "Shuō | to speak, to say"
    },
    {
      "question": "遍",
      "answer": "Biān | (for action) a time"
    },
    {
      "question": "打球",
      "answer": "Dǎqiú | to play ball games"
    },
    {
      "question": "打",
      "answer": "Dǎ | to play"
    },
    {
      "question": "球",
      "answer": "qiú | ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱歉",
      "answer": "Bàoqiàn | sorry"
    },
    {
      "question": "忙",
      "answer": "Máng | busy"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐怕",
      "answer": "Kǒngpà | afraid that..."
    },
    {
      "question": "行",
      "answer": "Xíng | to be OK"
    },
    {
      "question": "谢谢",
      "answer": "Xièxiè | to thank"
    },
    {
      "question": "你们",
      "answer": "Nǐmen | you (polite form)"
    }
  ]
}
